Kenneth C.M. Sills: Administrative Records A01.02.08
George J. Mitchell Department of Special Collections & Archives, Bowdoin College Library, Brunswick, Maine 04011
- World War II Correspondence, 1940-1946, A01.02.08.13; 42197; 5 Linear Feet
  - Barnes, Donald R. (Bow 1935), 42724 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Barron, Stanley P. (Bow 1940), 42725 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Barstow, Gilbert L. (Bow 1932), 42726 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bartlett, Thomas S. V. (1945), 42727 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Barton, William I. (Bow 1941), 42728 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bass, Robert N. (1940), 42729 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Bass, W. Streeter (Bow 1938), 42730 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Basset, Thomas E. (Bow 1937), 42731 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Batly, Walter S. (Bow 1937), 42732 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Baxter, John L. (1942), 42733 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Beal, George W. (Bow ch 1943), 42734 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bean, Emery O. (Bow 1940), 42735 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Beckett, George G. (Bow 1928), 42736 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Belknap, R. W. (Bow 1945), 42737 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Becker, Deforest (Bow ch 1946), 42738 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bell, Robert L. (1942 Bow), 42739 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Bellamy, William A. (Bow 1940), 42740 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Beneker, Benson V. (Bow 1936), 42741 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Benjamin, Francis B. (Bow 1936), 42742 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Benoit, E. Andre (Bow 1943), 42743 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Benson, John (Bow 1943), 42744 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Berkely, Austin W. (Bow 1936), 42745 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Berman, Malcolm (Bow 1946), 42746 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Berry, Arthur N. (Bow 1946), 42747 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Berry, H. M. (Bow 1941), 42748 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Berry, Richard (Bow 1945), 42749 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Bertels, B. Joseph (Bow 1939), 42750 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Bigelow, Walter K. (1935), 42751 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Bilodeau, Francis W. (Bow 1938), 42752 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bishop, Harold W. (Bow ch 1945), 42753 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Bishop, J.A. (Bow 1938), 42754 (Box 1, Folder 66a)
  - Blankenship, Stanford G. (Bow 1945), 42755 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Bliss, Francis R. (Bow 1940), 42756 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Blodgett, Frederic M. (Bow 1942), 42757 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Blodgett, Stephen B. (Bow 1942), 42758 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Bodwell, Howard (Bow 1929), 42759 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Bonney, Frank A. (Bow 1945), 42760 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Bonzagni, Henry V. (1941), 42761 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Booth, G. Russell (Bow 1938), 42762 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Bossidy, Bart H. (Bow 1933), 42763 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Boulter, Carl E. (Bow 1940), 42764 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Boutwell, Louis E. (Bow 1916), 42765 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Bowers, Charles H. (Bow 1942), 42766 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Bowman, Walter P. (Bow 1931), 42767 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Boyd, Richard M. (Bow 1933), 42768 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Boylston, Arthur G. (1944), 42769 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Bradford, Thomas M. (Bow 1937), 42770 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Bragdon, Roger W. (Bow 1943), 42771 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Brewer, Wilfred R. (Bow 1922), 42772 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Brewster, Charles R. (Bow 1937), 42773 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Brickates, Jeffrey E. (Bow 1940), 42774 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Briggs, G. D. (Bow 1933), 42775 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Brillante, Louis M. (Bow 1946), 42776 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Britton, Richard C. (Bow 1945), 42777 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Brockington, Harry F. (Bow 1946), 42778 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Brooks, John D. (Bow 1934), 42779 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Brown, Charles T. (Bow 1940), 42780 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Edward J. (1938), 42781 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Brown, George A. (Bow 1944), 42782 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Harold (Bow 1936), 42783 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Brown, Lewis W. (Bow 1920), 42784 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Brown, D. Preston (Bow ch 1941), 42785 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Brownell, Thomas A. (Bow 1941), 42786 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Brummer, Louis W. (Bow 1939), 42787 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bryant, Donald R. (Bow 1937), 42788 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bryant, M. David (Bow 1935), 42789 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bullock, Matthew W. (Bow 1940), 42790 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bunting, Henry S. (Bow 1943), 42791 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Burke, Philip B. (Bow 1944), 42792 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Burkett, George G., 42793 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Burnard, Edwin (Bow 1925), 42794 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Burnett, David, 42795 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Burpee, George A. (Bow 1945), 42796 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Burr, Edward B. (Bow 1945), 42797 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Burrows, Thomas E. (Bow 1929), 42798 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Burton, Robert S. (Bow 1943), 42799 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bush, Walter M. (Bow 1940), 42800 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Butler, F. Coit (Bow 1944), 42801 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Butler, Roland E. (Bow 1925), 42802 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Byron, Walter F. (Bow 1945), 42803 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Callahan, Daniel H. (Bow 1943), 42804 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Callman, I. B. (Bow 1944), 42805 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Campbell, Beverly (Bow 1946), 42806 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Campbell, Philip S. (Bow 1939), 42807 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Campbell, Wallace J. (Bow 1945), 42808 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Canavello, Frederick (Bow ch 1940), 42809 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Carey, Joseph F. (Bow 1944), 42810 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Carmichael, Douglass (Bow 1944), 42811 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Carr, Winthrop W. (1943), 42812 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Carrigan, Peter P. (Bow 1942), 42813 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Carter, George (Bow 1935), 42814 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Carter, W. Hodding (Bow 1927), 42815 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Cartland, John E. Jr. (Bow 1939), 42816 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Cass, M. W. (Bow 1937), 42817 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Cay, Donald F. (Bow 1943), 42818 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Chamberland, Malcolm (Bow 1946), 42819 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Chandler, Robert E. (Bow 1941), 42820 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Chapen, John (Bow 1941), 42821 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Chapman, H. Philip Jr. (Bow 1930), 42822 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Chapman, Philip F. Jr. (1938 Bow), 42823 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Chase, Charles W. (Bow 1932), 42824 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Cheetham, William H., 42825 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Chisholm, George E. (Bow 1936), 42826 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Chism, Murray F. (Bow 1942), 42827 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Cing-Mars, Robert J. (Bow 1943), 42828 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Claff, Leslie A. (Bow 1926), 42829 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Clark, Freeman D. (Bow 1938), 42830 (Box 2, Folder 50a)
  - Clark, Harry B. (Bow 1936), 42831 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Clark, Robert S. (Bow 1929), 42832 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Clark, Thomas D. (Bow 1926), 42833 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Clarke, Clinton B. (Bow 1946), 42834 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Clarke, Raymond M. (Bow 1947), 42835 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cleaves, Fort B. (Bow 1932), 42836 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Cleaves, George M. (Bow 1934), 42837 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Cleaves, Robert A. (Bow 1935), 42838 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Clenott, William (Bow 1946), 42839 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Clive, Frederick T. (Bow 1945), 42840 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Clogston, R. Benjamin (Bow 1933), 42841 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Cobb, Richard W. (Bow 1922), 42842 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Coburn, John W. (Bow 1919), 42843 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Coffin, Robert P. T. Jr., 42844 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Cohen, Leonard (Bow 1939), 42845 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Coit, Charles A., 42846 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Cole, Charles W. (Bow n 1927), 42847 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Cole, Philip (Bow 1912), 42848 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Cole, Philip Jr. (Bow ch 1943), 42849 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Cole, Taylor (Bow 1945), 42850 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Colton, Robert E. (Bow 1944), 42851 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Conant, Donald B. (Bow 1941), 42852 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Congdon, John (Bow 1943), 42853 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Connor, Brian (Bow 1927), 42854 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Coombs, Robert W. (Bow 1940), 42855 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Cooper, Edward W. (Bow 1941), 42856 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Cooper, Thomas A. (Bow 1944), 42857 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Cormack, Warren E. (Bow 1946), 42858 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Cowan, Casper F. (Bow 1936), 42859 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Cowley, Wilbur, 42860 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Craig, John H. (Bow 1941), 42861 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Crain, Charles M. (Bow 1946), 42862 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Crowen, John V. (Bow 1943), 42863 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Crawford, A. Chandler (Bow 1937), 42864 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Creighton, John (Bow 1942), 42865 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Cressey, Stanley B. (Bow 1940), 42866 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Cronin, Joseph S. (Bow 1943), 42867 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Cronkhite, Leonard W. (Bow 1941), 42868 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Cross, Harold L. (Bow 1937), 42869 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cross, Robert (Bow 1945), 42870 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Crossman, Mortimer B. (Bow 1920), 42871 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Crowell, James D. (Bow 1935), 42872 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Curry, John J. (Bow 1946), 42873 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Curtis, Charles W. (Bow 1947), 42874 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Curtis, John A. (Bow 1945), 42875 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dana, Edward F. (Bow 1929), 42876 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dana, Lawrence (Bow 1935), 42877 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dane, Francis S. Jr. (Bow 1931), 42878 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Davidson, George T. (Bow 1938), 42879 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Davidson, Paul L. (Bow ch 1945), 42880 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Davis, Evan G. (Bow 1938), 42881 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Davis, Frank R. (Bow 1941), 42882 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Davis, Hubert V. (Bow 1923), 42883 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Davis, M. Ben (Bow 1926), 42884 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Davis, Nicholas (Bow ch 1946), 42885 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Richard H. (Bow 1934), 42886 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Davis, Stuart K. (Bow 1935), 42887 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Davis, William H. (Bow 1939), 42888 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Davis, William M. (Bow 1949), 42889 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Davison, Howard A. (Bow 1930), 42890 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Dawson, George R. (Bow 1945), 42891 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Dean, William H. (1930), 42892 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Dell, Russell C. (Bow 1936), 42893 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Demarest, Lawrence M. (Bow 1945), 42894 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Denham, Enos M. (Bow 1939), 42895 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Denison, Orville B. (Bow 1941), 42896 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Denismore, M. A. (Bow 1946), 42897 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - de Sherbmin, Robert I. (Bow 1945), 42898 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Devine, Donald T. (Bow 1943), 42899 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Dick, John A. (Bow 1945), 42900 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Dickson, David (Bow 1941), 42901 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Dolan, Henry A. (Bow 1949), 42902 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Dolan, James D. (Bow 1943), 42903 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Donahue, Walter S. (Bow 1944), 42904 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Donaldson, John (Bow 1944), 42905 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Donavan, Peter (Bow 1940), 42906 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Donovan, Timothy (Bow 1948), 42907 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Donworth, John S. (Bow 1931), 42908 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Doubleday, James A. (Bow 1941), 42909 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Dougherty, William A. (Bow 1946), 42910 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Douglas, Paul H. (Bow 1913), 42911 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Downs, Thomas L. (Bow 1927), 42912 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Doyle, Elliot L. (Bow 1928), 42913 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Doyle, Richard (Bow 1940), 42914 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Drake, B. W. (Bow 1945), 42915 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Draper, James B. (Bow 1949), 42916 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Driscoll, Francis J. (Bow 1942), 42917 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Dufton, George F. (Bow 1930), 42918 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Duggan, Norman E. (Bow 1944), 42919 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Dunbar, George A. (Bow 1939), 42920 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Dunbar, Roger D. (Bow 1941), 42921 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Dunlap, Edward A. III (Bow 1940), 42922 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Dunn, Leo J. (Bow 1947), 42923 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Durant, E. T. (Bow 1928), 42924 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Dwelley, H. R. (Bow 1949), 42925 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Dyer, J. Donald (Bow 1937)?, 42926 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Dyment, Harold E. (Bow 1940), 42927 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Eames, Paul H. Jr. (Bow 1946), 42928 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Early, James (Bow 1945), 42929 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Eastman, R. Kimball Jr. (Bow 1944)?, 42930 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Eaton, Franklin (Bow 1942), 42931 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Eaton, Maxwell A. (Bow 1937), 42932 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Eck, Arnold R. (Bow 1942), 42933 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Ecke, Robert S. (Bow 1931), 42934 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Eckfeldt, Roger W. (Bow 1943), 42935 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Eddy, Warren Jr. (Bow 1943), 42936 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Edwards, Alfred B. (Bow 1932), 42937 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Edwards, Charles P. (Bow 1941), 42938 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Edwards, Robert L. (Bow 1943), 42939 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Edwards, Roger, 42940 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Eklund, Wilhelm C. (Bow 1941), 42941 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Eliot, William L. (Bow 1944), 42942 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Elliot, R. Bruce (Bow 1945), 42943 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Elliot, W. N. (Bow 1943), 42944 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Elliott, C. James (Bow ch 1941), 42945 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Elliott, Gilbert M. Jr. (Bow 1925), 42946 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Ellis, Robert W. (Bow 1941), 42947 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Evans, John C. (Bow 1941), 42948 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Eveleth, Richard T. (Bow 1941), 42949 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Evens, Delos W. (Bow 1932), 42950 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Everett, Edward F. (Bow 1940), 42951 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Evers, Wallace K. (Bow 1946), 42952 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Falconer, Robert C. (Bow 1937), 42953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Farley, Charles H. (Bow 1930), 42954 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Farr, Henry L. (Bow 1929), 42955 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Farrington, Hugh F. (Bow ch 1944), 42956 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fay, John G. (Bow 1934), 42957 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fearon, Harold R. (Bow 1936), 42958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ferris, Alden C. (Bow 1939), 42959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Field, R. C. (Bow 1946), 42960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Finnagan, Waller P. (Bow 1945), 42961 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fish, William H. (Bow 1943), 42962 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fisher, Stanwood E. Jr. (Bow 1941), 42963 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Fitts, David W. (Bow 1938), 42964 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Flanagan, J. V. (Bow 1946), 42965 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Flint, Putnam P. (Bow 1942), 42966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Flint, Vasmer L. (Bow 1938), 42967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Flynt, William F. (Bow 1944), 42968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Fogg, George E. Jr. (Bow 1943), 42969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fogg, Sanford L. Jr. (Bow 1927), 42970 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Foran, John (Bow 1946), 42971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Forbes, John R. (Bow 1938), 42972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Fortin, Christian, 42973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Foster, Robert J. (Bow 1925), 42974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Foster, Robert M. (1934), 42975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Fox, Robert B. (Bow 1938), 42976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Frazier, Claude R. (Bow 1938), 42977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Freeman, James C. (Bow 1934), 42978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Freese, John B. (Bow 1918), 42979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Freme, Ferris A. (Bow 1942), 42980 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Friedmann, John R. P. (Bow 1947), 42981 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Frost, Stevens L. (Bow 1942), 42982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Fry, William F. (Bow 1946), 42983 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Frye, John H. (Bow 1938), 42984 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Gammon, Alan L. (Bow 1943), 42985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Gardner, Richard F. (Bow 1942), 42986 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Garvey, Edward C. (Bow 1945), 42987 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Gates, Ellis L. (Bow 1937), 42988 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Gates, Philip B. (Bow 1940), 42989 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Gatterer (Gordon), Herbert G. (Bow 1940), 42990 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Gauvreau, Norman O. (Bow 1943), 42991 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Gentry, Newell E. (Bow 1940), 42992 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Gillett, Newell E. (Bow 1940), 42993 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Gilman, Elvin J. (Bow 1940), 42994 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Gilpatrick, Paul H. (Bow 1937), 42995 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Gingras, Richard C. (Bow 1944), 42996 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Girard, Wilfred H. (Bow 1939), 42997 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Golden, Balfour H. (Bow 1944), 42998 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Golderman, Robert W. (Bow 1947), 42999 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Goldman, Jack D. (Bow 1937), 43000 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Gordon, Herbert G. (Bow 1940), 43001 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Gordon, Robert G. (Bow 1941), 43002 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Goudouros, James T. (Bow 1946), 43003 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Gould, Albert P. (Bow 1937), 43004 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Gray, Deane B. (Bow 1942), 43005 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Gray, Eldon (Bow 1926), 43006 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Greene, Horace S. (Bow 1939), 43007 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Greene, William M. (Bow ch 1946), 43008 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Greenly, J. A. (Bow 1945), 43009 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Gregory, Alfred L. (Bow 1943), 43010 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Griffith, George M. (Bow 1937), 43011 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Griffith, Joseph H. (Bow 1940), 43012 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Guy, Basil J. (Bow 1947), 43013 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Gwynn, Frederick L. (Bow 1937), 43014 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Hackwell, R. Lloyd (Bow 1934), 43015 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Haldane, Andrew A. (Bow 1941), 43016 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Hale, Richard F. (Bow ch 1944), 43017 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Hales, James A. (Bow 1940), 43018 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Haley, Bruce T. (Bow 1941), 43019 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Hall, W. Bradford (Bow 1941), 43020 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Hall, Crowell T. (Bow 1937), 43021 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Hall, Frederick W. (Bow 1942), 43022 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Hall, James B. (Bow 1947), 43023 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Hall, Peter A., 43024 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Hall, W. B. (Bow 1941), 43025 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Hamblen, Arthur (Bow 1948), 43026 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Hanscom, Ward T. (Bow 1941), 43027 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Hanson, Arthur W. (Bow 1941), 43028 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Hanson, Richard C. (Bow 1942), 43029 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Happ, William (Bow 1946), 43030 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Harding, R. R. (Bow 1941), 43031 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Harkness, Robert (Bow 1926), 43032 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Harrington, Robert W. (Bow 1934), 43033 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Hartshorn, Charles (Bow 1941), 43034 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Hastings, Merrill G. (Bow ch 1914), 43035 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Hatch, Lloyd H. (Bow 1940), 43036 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Hathaway, Alton H. (Bow 1933), 43037 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Hauserman, Frank B. (Bow 1945), 43038 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hawkins, William S. (Bow 1938), 43039 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hawke, Edward A. (Bow 1946), 43040 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hayes, Paul T. (Bow 1931), 43041 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hayward, Ralph C. (Bow 1943), 43042 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Heflin, Robert D. (Bow 1943), 43043 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hellman, Alan G. (Bow ch 1944), 43044 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Henderson, C. F. C. (Bow 1937), 43045 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Hendrickson, Harold M. (Bow 1942), 43046 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hermann, Paul H. (Bow 1940), 43047 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Herrick, James E. (Bow 1945), 43048 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Herron, Philip W. (Bow 1946), 43049 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Hersey, Francis C. (Bow 1946), 43050 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hess, John E. (Bow 1944), 43051 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Heussler, John M. (Bow 1946), 43052 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Heymann, Alfred L. (Bow 1945), 43053 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Heymann, Melvin (Bow 1948), 43054 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Heywood, George H. (Bow 1943), 43055 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Hickox, John B. (Bow 1934), 43056 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Higgins, J. R. (Bow 1943), 43057 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hill, Calvin A. (Bow 1940), 43058 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hill, Robert B. (Bow 1942), 43059 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Hills, Leonard (Bow 1943), 43060 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hinkley, Walter (Bow 1934), 43061 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hirch, Leonard W. (Bow 1947), 43062 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Holden, Dudley F. (Bow 1938), 43063 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Holmes, Alonzo B. (Bow 1921), 43064 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Holmes, Clyde B. (Bow 1940), 43065 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Holtman, Frank G. (Bow 1947), 43066 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Holway, William G. (Bow 1926), 43067 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Hopkins, John S. (Bow 1927), 43068 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Hormell, Robert S., 43069 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Houghton, Charles F. (Bow 1915), 43070 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Howard, Edward R. (Bow ch 1941), 43071 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Howard, Henry M. (Bow 1918), 43072 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Howard, Marshall H. A. (Bow ch 1945), 43073 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Howard, Thomas W. (Bow 1939), 43074 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Hudon, Edward G. (Bow 1937), and Louis J. (Bow 1938), 43075 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Hughes, Albert (Bow 1939), 43076 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Hunt, Emerson W. (Bow 1923), 43077 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Hunt, Enoch W. (Bow 1934), 43078 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Hunt, Mansfield L. (Bow 1937), 43079 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Hunter, James B. (Bow 1939), 43080 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Hupper, John R. (Bow 1950), 43081 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Hussey, Stetson H. Jr. (Bow 1941), 43082 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Hutchings, George W. (Bow 1943), 43083 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Hutchinson, Melville C. (Bow 1939), 43084 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Hyde, Richard W. (Bow 1943), 43085 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Ingalls, Roscoe C. (Bow 1943), 43086 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Ireland, Charles T. (Bow 1942), 43087 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Irish, James T. Jr. (Bow 1945), 43088 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - "Jack" (?), 43089 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Jack, Paul E. (Bow 1933), 43090 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Jackson, Henry B. (Bow 1936), 43091 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - James, David A. (Bow 1943), 43092 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Janney, Raymond Barton (Bow 1942), 43093 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Jenkisson, John F. (Bow 1941), 43094 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Johnson, Joseph H. (Bow 1944), 43095 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Johnson, Philip M. (Bow 1940), 43096 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Johnson, Robert L., 43097 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Johnston, David B. (Bow 1945), 43098 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Johnston, R. C., 43099 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Johnstone, Richard C. (Bow 1944), 43100 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Jones, F. P. (Bow 1946), 43101 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Joy, Ernest H. (Bow 1925), 43102 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Joy, Franklin L. (Bow 1944), 43103 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Jurgenson, Robert G. (Bow 1945), 43104 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Kahill, Charles F. (Bow 1934), 43105 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Kane, Howard F. (Bow 1909), 43106 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Kane, James A. (Bow 1941), 43107 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Karsokas, B. H. (Bow 1939), 43108 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Keefe, Thaddeus K. (Bow 1941), 43109 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Keene, B. E. (Bow 1947), 43110 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Kelley, Forbes W. (Bow 1941), 43111 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Kelly, John J. (Bow 1935), 43112 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Kendruck, Albert S., 43113 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Kennedy, Robert M. (Bow 1942), 43114 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Keniston, Allan G. (Bow 1944), 43115 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Kent, George G. (Bow 1947), 43116 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Keylor, Arthur W. (Bow 1942), 43117 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Kidd, Ralph E. (Bow 1943), 43118 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Kileski, Frederick G. (Bow 1920), 43119 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Kimball, J. Frank (Bow 1947), 43120 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Kinnard J. R. (Bow 1941), 43121 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Kinsey, Charles (Bow 1940), 43122 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Kinsley, Samuel E. (Bow 1946), 43123 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Kitfield, David B. (Bow 1946), 43124 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Knight, Lendall B. (Bow 1941), 43125 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Knox, C. A. (Bow 1931), 43126 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Kyle, Kim (Bow 1947), 43127 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Lackey, William S. (Bow 1937), 43128 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - LaFond, Paul D. (Bow 1943), 43129 (Box 5, Folder 92)